You may now kiss the decoy.
The Decoy Bride is a drama, comedy, romance film directed by Sheree Folkson.
A local woman is hired to draw paparazzi away from a Hollywood
actress who has come to Scotland to get married.
Katie Meaghaid, played by Kelly Macdonald.
Lara Tyler, played by Alice Eve.
James Arber, played by David Tennant.
Steve, played by Michael Urie.
Marco, played by Federico Castelluccio.
Security guard, played by Gil Kolirin.
The Decoy Bride is a 2011 British romantic comedy film written by comedian Sally Phillips and Neil Jaworski, and starring Kelly Macdonald,
David Tennant, and Alice Eve and set on the fictional island of Hegg, supposedly located in the Outer Hebrides of Scotland.
The film was made by Ecosse Films.
The film explores themes of island, scotland, paparazzi, decoy, wedding.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.